Guide to the Stanford University, W. W. Hansen Laboratories of Physics, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- MILLIMETER GENERATION AND NON-LINEAR PROPAGATION IN FERROMAGNETICS
  - Continuation Proposal for October 1, 1963 through September 30, 1964, (DA 36(039)AMC-00041 (E)), August 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Continuation Proposal for High Power Millimeter Generation and Basic Studies in Ferromagnetics by Shaw for October 1, 1963 through September 30, 1964, (DA 36(039)AMC-00041 (E)), June 1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Continuation of Research on Pulsed Magnetic Field Millimeter Wave Generators (formerly SC-85263), (DA 36 (039) AMC-00041 (E)), June 1962 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Transfer of Property from contract DA 36(039) SC-85263, (DA 36(039)AMC-00041 (E)), June 1963 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Final Property Accounting, (DA 36 (039) AMC-00041 (E)), August 1965 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- OPTICAL TRANSITION PROBABILITIES IN SOLIDS AND METHODS OF MODULATING THEM
  - Grant Agreement, (DA Grant DA-ARO (D)-31-124-G449), May 1963 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - A Study of Optical Transition Probabilities in Solids and of Methods of Modulating them, (DA Grant DA-ARO (D)-31-124-G449), May 1963 - April 1964 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- $30,000 TRANSFERRED FROM S.E.L.
  - $30,000 Transferred from S.E.L. for Work under their Contract, (DA 36 (039) AMC-00094 (E)), April 27, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- DESIGN, DEVELOPMENT AND TESTING OF A MEDICAL LINEAR ACCELERATOR FOR HIGH-ENERGY RADIATION THERAPY
  - USPHS Application for Grant C-1566 (C3) for 1955-56 (USPHS Grant C-1566), March 1955 - August 1955 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - USPHS Grant C-1566 (C2) for 1954-55, (USPHS Grant C-1566), August 1955 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - USPHS Grant C-1566 (C2), Intrim Report for September, 1954 through March, 1955 (USPHS Grant C-1566) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - USPHS Appliation for Grant C-1566 (C2) for 1954-55 and Interim Report for September, 1953 through May, 1954, (USPHS Grant C-1566), February - May 1954 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - USPHS Grant C-1566C for September 1, 1953 through August 31, 1954, (USPHS Grant C-1566), February - March 1954 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - USPHS Grant C-1566 for May 1, 1952 through March 30, 1953, (USPHS Grant C-1566), February - December 1952 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- EXPERIMENTAL BASIS OF CLINICAL RADIATION THERAPY
  - USPHS Grant C-3353 (C2) for April, 1959 through March, 1960 by Kaplan and Burns, (USPHS Grant C-3353), April 1959 - March 1960 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - USPHS Grant C-3353 (C1) for April, 1958 through March, 1959 by Kaplan and Burns, (USPHS Grant C-3353), April 1958 - March 1959 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - USPHS Grant C-3353 for April, 1957 through March, 1958 by Kaplan, (USPHS Grant C-3353), April 1957 - March 1958 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- DEVELOPMENT AND APPLICATION OF X-RAY MICROSCOPY
  - Grant RG-4937 (C1) for January, 1958 through December, 1958 by Kirkpatrick and Pattee, (USPHS Grant RG-4937), July - September 1959 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Grant RG-4937 Documents. Predecessor of USPHS Grant A-2557. (USPHS Grant RG-4937), June 1956 - January 1958 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- PHYSICAL METHODS OF CYTOCHEMICAL ANALYSIS
  - USPHS Grant A-2557 (C4) for January, 1961 through December 1961 by Pattee, (USPHS Grant A-2557 (B.B.C.), January- December 1961 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - USPHS Grant A-2557 (C3) for January, 1960 through December 1960 by Pattee, (USPHS Grant A-2557 (B.B.C.), January- December 1960 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - USPHS Grant A-2557 (C2) for January, 1959 through December 1959 by Pattee, (USPHS Grant A-2557 (B.B.C.), January- December 1959 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - USPHS Grant A-2557 (C) for January, 1958 through December 1958 by Pattee, (USPHS Grant A-2557 (B.B.C.), January- December 1958 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- BIOPHYSICS OF FREE RADICALS AND ANTIOXIDANTS
  - USPHS Grant A-2304 (C3) (B.B.C.) for September, 1961 through August, 1962 by Blois (USPHS Grant A-2304 (B.B.C.)) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - USPHS Grant A-2304 (C2) (B.B.C.) for September, 1960 through August, 1961 by Blois (USPHS Grant A-2304 (B.B.C.)) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - USPHS Grant A-2304 (C1) (B.B.C.) for September, 1959 through August, 1960 by Blois (USPHS Grant A-2304 (B.B.C.)) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - USPHS Grant A-2304 (B.B.C.) for September, 1958 through August, 1959 by Blois (USPHS Grant A-2304 (B.B.C.) (Box 27, Folder 4)
- BIOPHYSICAL STUDIES OF CELL DIVISION AND INTRACELLULAR COORDINATION
  - Grant AM 03727-05 for December 1, 1963 through November 30, 1964 by Burns, (USPHS Grant A-3727), June 1963 - October 1966 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Grant AM 03727-04 for December 1, 1962 through November 30, 1963 by Burns, (USPHS Grant A-3727), December 1962 - November 1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Grant A-3727 (C2) for December 1, 1961 through November 30, 1962 by Burns, (USPHS Grant A-3727), December 1961 - November 1962 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Grant A-3727 (C1) for December 1, 1960 through November 30, 1961 by Burns, (USPHS Grant A-3727), December 1960 - November 1961 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Grant A-3727 for December 1, 1959 through November 30, 1960 by Burns, (USPHS Grant A-3727), December 1959 - November 1960 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- PHYSICAL CHEMISTRY OF ENZYME SPECIFICITY
  - Dartmouth USPHS Grant H-3600 (C3) by Jacobs, Stanford Account No. 62-448144, November 1960 - March 1962 (USPHS Grant 3600) (Box 27, Folder 10)
- BIOLOGICAL AND MEDICAL INVESTIGATIONS AND RELATED WORK WITH THE HIGH-ENERGY LINEAR ELECTRON ACCELERATOR, MARK IV
  - Contract and Amendments, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), July 1954 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - General, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), December 1955 - December 1960 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Extension to December 31, 1960, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), August 1960 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Extension Proposal for October, 1959 through September, 1960, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A.2), July 1959 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Extension Proposal for October, 1958 through September, 1959, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A.2), June 1958 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Extension Proposal for October, 1957 through September, 1958, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A.2), June 1957 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Extension Proposal for June 30, 1956 through June 30, 1957, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), May 1956 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Extension Proposal for June 30, 1955 through June 30, 1956, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), March 1955 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Radiobiological Proposal, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), April 1954 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - RAdiobiological Proposal, no action, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), June 1953 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Memo: Development of 50 MEV Accelerator and Use in Radiobiology, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A.2), February 1953 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Supplement #2, Requirements, etc., (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), July 1955 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Alien Reports, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), May 1960 - November 1961 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Annual Physical Inventory, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), Septemeber 1959 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), June 1958 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), June 1957 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory of Plant Equipment, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), June 1956 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Interim Physical Inventory, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), May 1955 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Physical Inventory and Listing, September 1959, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), May 1958 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Final Technical Report, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), December 1960 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Disposition of Property, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), September 1961 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Final Inventory, (AT(04-3)-21 P.A.2), February 1961 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Final Property Accounting, (AT (04-3)-21 P.A. 2), February 1961 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- SPECTROMETER STUDY
  - Spectrometer Study by Panofsky, (NSF Grant G-1229), November 1954 - August 1956 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- NON-PERIODIC CIRCUIT R-F INTERACTION WITH SLOW-MOVING ELECTRONS
  - Non-Periodic Circuit R-F Interaction with Slow-Moving Electrons by Pantell, (NSF Grant G 6316), March 1958 - March 1963 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- G-VALUES OF BIOLOGICAL FREE RADICALS
  - Research Grant by Blois, (NSF Grant G-14367), August 1960 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Research Proposal by Blois, (NSF Grant G-14367), February 1960 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- RF INTERACTION WITH SLOW-MOVING ELECTRONS
  - RF Interaction with Slow-Moving Electrons by Pantrell, (NSF Grant G-15011), November 1960 - November 1963 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- STUDIES AND EXPERIMENTS ON THE DESIGN OF AN IRON-FREE SOLENOIDAL SPECTROMETER
  - Studies and Experiments on the Design of an Iron-Free Solenoidal Spectrometer by Hofstadter May 1, 1961 - May 30, 1962 (NSF Grant G-17620) (Box 28, Folder 16)
- PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE THIRD INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON X-RAY OPTICS AND X-RAY MICROANALYSIS
  - Partial Support of the Third International Symposium on X-Ray Optics and X-Ray Microanalysis, August 22-24, 1962, (NSF Grant G-23080), March 1962 - February 1963 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- NONLINEAR INTERACTION BETWEEN RADIATION AND SYSTEMS WITH QUANTIZED ENERGY LEVELS
  - Nonlinear Interaction between Radiation and Systems with Quantized Energy Levels, by Pantell, (NSF Grant G-22929), September 1961 - December 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- U-V AND MOSSBAUER STUDIES IN MACROMOLECULES
  - U-V and Mossbauer Studies in Macromolecules, by Weissbluth, (NSF Grant G-24006), December 1961 - March 1964 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- ELECTRON PARAMAGNETIC RESONANCE STUDY OF UNPAIRED ELECTRONS IN PHOTOSYNTHETIC MUTANT AND WILDTYPE ORGANISMS
  - Electron Paramagnetic Resonance Study of Unpaired Electrons in Photosynthetic Mutant and Wildtype Organisms, (ACS Grant P-170), January 1963 - May 1965 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- MICROCHEMICAL ANALYSIS OF BIOLOGICAL SPECIMENS USING THE X-RAY MICROSCOPE
  - Microchemical Analysis of Biological Specimens Using the X-Ray Microscope, by Pattee, (ACS Grant P-170), February 1958 - October 1959 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- THE QUANTITATIVE MASS DENSITY MEASUREMENT IN TISSUE BY X-RAY MICROSCOPY
  - The Quantitative Mass Density Measurement in Tissue by X-Ray Microscopy, by Pattee, (ACS Grant P-165), February 1958 - October 1959 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- DESIGN, DEVELOPMENT, AND TESTING OF A MEDICAL LINEAR ELECTRON ACCELERATOR FOR HIGH-ENERGY RADIATION THERAPY
  - ACS Grant INSP-65D for September 1, 1956 through August 31, 1957 by Ginzton and Kaplan, (ACS Grant INSP-65), April 1956 - March 1958 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - ACS Application for Grant, 1956 - 1957 by Ginzton and Kaplan, (ACS Grant INSP-65), May 1956 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - ACS Grant INSP-65C for September 1, 1955 through August 31, 1956 by Ginzton, (ACS Grant INSP-65), August 1955 - January 1957 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - ACS Application for Renewal of INSP-65B for September 1, 1955 through August 31, 1956, (ACS Grant INSP-65), May 1955 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - ACS Grant INSP-65B for September 1, 1954 through August 31, 1955, (ACS Grant INSP-65), June 1954 - November 1955 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - ACS Application for Renewal of INSP-65A for September 1, 1954 through August 31, 1955, (ACS Grant INSP-65), April 1954 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - ACS Grant INSP-65A for September 1, 1953 through August 31, 1954, (ACS Grant INSP-65), August 1953 - November 1954 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - ACS Application for Renewal of INSTR-65 for September 1, 1953 through August 31, 1954, (ACS Grant INSP-65), May 1953 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- FREE RADICALS
  - ACS Grant INSTR-78D for February 13, 1958 through August 31, 1958 by Weissbluth on Short-lived Free Radicals, (ACS Grant INSTR-78), December 1957 - July 1958 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Machine Work for R. Lowvinger under Stanford Hospital Reqn. 74945, (ACS Grant INSTR-78), March 1958 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - ACS Institution INSTR-78C, Account 70-4431-35, for September 1, 1956 through August 31, 1957 by Blois, (ACS Grant INSTR-78), November 1956 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - ACS Grant INSTR-78A for March 24, 1955 through August 31, 1955 by Blois on Free Radicals in Biological Materials, (ACS Grant INSTR-78), March 1955 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- FREE RADICALS AND ANTIOXIDANTS IN CARCINOGENESIS
  - ACS Application by Blois. Accepted by ACS with a Reduced Level of Support and therefore rejected by the Lab, April 1957 - September 1957 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- USE OF A NEGATIVE PION BEAM FOR CANCER THERAPY
  - Use of a Negative Pion Beam for Cancer Therapy, by Weissbluth and Richman, (ACS Grant T-281), April 1963 - December 1964 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- RESEARCH UNDER THE DIRECTION OF EARL JACOBS
  - AHA Grant 57 F 105 E for July 1, 1961 through June 30, 1963 by Jacobs, (AHA Grant 57 F 105 E), March 1961 - April 1965 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- TRAVEL FOR EARL JACOBS TO STOCKHOLM AND MOSCOW
  - AHA Grant 61 G 158 for July 1, 1961 through June 30, 1962 by Jacobs, (AHA Grant 61 G 158), July 1961 - June 1962 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- CHARACTERIZATION OF PHOSPHORYLATION COUPLED TO ELECTRON TRANSPORT PROCESSES IN CYTOCHROME OXIDASE
  - AHA Grant 61 G 136 for July 1, 1961 through June 30, 1963 by Jacobs, (AHA Grant 61 G 136), July 1961 - June 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- A STUDY OF SYSTEMS FOR SPACE PROPULSION
  - Contract and Amendments, (NAS 8-1509), February 1961 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, (NAS 8-1509), March 1961 - July 1966 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Proposal for Extension for May 1, 1963 through April 30, 1964, (NAS 8-1509), February 1963 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Informal Requests to Extend the Scope of the Contract, by G.Kino, (NAS 8-1509), November 1962 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Revised Proposal to NASA to EXtend Contract NAS 8-1509 for December 1, 1961 through August 31, 1962, (NAS 8-1509), March 1962 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Proposal for Extension to August 31, 1962, (NAS 8-1509), November 1961 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Proposal to NASA for a Contract for a Study of Systems for Space Propulsion, May 1960. Revised November 1960. (NAS 8-1509), May 1960 - April 1961 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Final Property Accounting, (NAS 8-1509), November 1963 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- MOLECULAR EVOLUTION IN PROTOBIOLOGICAL SYSTEMS
  - Molecular Evolution in Protobiological Systems, etc. by Blois, (NASA Grant NsG 218-62), December 1961 - March 1965 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- THEORETICAL STUDIES OF TURBULENCE IN PLASMAS
  - Theoretical Studies of Turbulence in Plasmas by Sturrock, (NASA Grant NsG 703), January 1964 - April 1965 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- SEALED LINEAR ACCELERATOR WAVEGUIDE, AND PULSE TRANSFORMER
  - General Electric P.O. XR-12304, January 1954 - April 1956 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- ELECTRON GUNS FOR MEDICAL ACCELERATORS PROGRAM
  - General Electric P.O. XR-22715, March 1955 - October 1956 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- MEDICAL ACCELERATOR COMPONENTS
  - General Electric P.O. XR-22718, March 1955 - October 1956 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- FINANCIAL HISTORY
  - Transfer of Funds for General Electric XR-12304, XR-22715, XR-22718, April 1954 - August 1956 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- RESEARCH ON FREQUENCY MULTIPLIER TUBE
  - General Electric Co. Microwave Laboratory P.O. No. EIM 270-1528 (Prime AF 04(645)-12), January 1956 - December 1958 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- FURTHER THE USE OF LINEAR ELECTRON ACCELERATORS IN MEDICAL RESEARCH
  - Albert J. Thille Fund for Medical Physics Research, June 1953 - June 1962 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- SPERRY GYROSCOPE MICROWAVE RESEARCH RESERVE FUND
  - Sperry Gyroscope Microwave Research Reserve Fund, (Sperry Account 4431-12), December 1951 - December 1954 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- CONSTRUCTION OF A LINEAR ACCELERATOR (SLAC)
  - Project M Development Account, (Project M Development Account 4431-02), November 1956 - February 1961 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- HARVARD UNIVERSITY P.O. NO. V-24863
  - L.H. Hand, Experiment on Electron-Proton and Electron-Deuteron Comparison, (Harvard University AT (30-1)-2752), April 1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- KLYSTRON PURCHASE AGREEMENT
  - Klystron Purchase Agreement, (University of California Purchase Agreement), July 1953 - April 1955 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- HANSEN LABS IMPROVEMENT
  - Equipment Appropriation, (Special Authorization 132), 1955 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- FABRICATE, TEST AND DELIVER TO VARIAN ASSOCIATES SEVERAL COMPONENTS FOR AN ACCELERATOR SIMILAR TO THE STANFORD ACCELERATOR
  - Purchase Order B30083, Account No. 4086-01, (Varian Associates P.O. B30083), June 1956 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- ELECTROFORM FOUR ACCELERATOR SECTIONS
  - Purchase Order 13770, (Varian Associates P.O. 13770), April 1958 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- MEDICAL ACCELERATOR IMPROVEMENTS
  - Medical Accelerator Improvements by Weissbluth, (Medical Accelerator Improvements Account 3611-75), December 1958 - April 1961 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- BRITISH EMPIRE CANCER CAMPAIGN FELLOWSHIP
  - British Empire Cancer Campaign Fellowship, Dr. Wyard, January 1961 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- NATIONAL BUREAU OF STANDARDS TARGETS PURCHASE ORDER
  - National Bureau of Standards Targets Purchase Order, (National Bureau of Standards P.O. S-124388-65), February 1964 - March 1965 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1951
  - USPHS Application for "Design, Development and Testing of a Medical Linear Electron Accelerator for High Energy Radiation Therapy", May 1951 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1954
  - NSF Proposal for "Design Study for High-Energy Magnetic Spectrometers", July 1954 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1957
  - ACS Application for "Free Radicals and Antioxidants in Carcinogenesis" by Blois. Accepted by ACS with a Reduced Level of Support and therefore Rejected by the Lab, (Located in Files with ACS Grants), April 1957
  - ERL Proposal to Rome Air Force Center for "Research and Development on Microwave Tubes with Particular Application to Electronic Countermeasures", September 1957 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1958
  - Tentative Proposal to Replace SEL Support of Microwave Lab Work. Signal Corps, June 1958 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Proposal to San Antonio R&D Procurement Office, ARDC, for "Research on Free Radicals" by Blois, June 1958 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - NSF Proposal for "Research in Nonlinear `Neoclassical' Electrodynamics, July 1958 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Proposal to OSR for Aquisition of Pulsed Magnetic Field Generator, July 1958 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1960
  - Tentative Proposal to ONR for "Pilot Study of Molecular Evolution", March 1960 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Proposal to ONR for "A Program of Research on Electrodynamic Problems of Astrophysics", April 1960 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Proposal to NSF for "A Program of Research on Electrodynamic Problems of Astrophysics", April 1960 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Proposal to AFOSR for "A Program of Research on Electrodynamic Problems of Astrophysics", April 1960 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Proposal to ONR for "An Investigation of the Precision Determination of the g-Values of Biological Free Radicals", by Blois, July 1960 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Proposal to RADC for A Study of the Microwave Properties of Plasmas, by Chodorow, December 1960 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1961
  - Proposal to Wright Air Development Division for Research on Millimeter Wave Generation Using the Fact Wave Principle, by Chodorow and Pantell, January 1961 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Application to NSF for A Logical and Statistical Analysis of Order-Producing Mechanisms in Macromolecular Sequence, by Pattee, May 1961 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Application to USPHS for Partial Cell Infrared Microspectroscopy, by Pattee, October 1961 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1962
  - Research Proposal to NSF for Investigation of Ordering Processes in Macromolecular Sequences by Pattee, May 1962 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Application for USPHS Grant for U-V Absorption and Mossbauer Effect in Macromolecules, by Weissbluth, May 1962 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Proposal to the Advanced Research Projects Agency for A Program of Research on Basic Plasma Phenomena, September 1962 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Proposal to the National Aeronautics and Space Administration for Research on Basic Plasma Phenomena, October 1962 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Informal Proposal to Wright-Patterson for Study of a Possible Method of Modulating Light at Frequencies Exceeding 100 kMc by Means of the Franz-Keldysh Effect in a Semiconductor, by Coleman, December 1962 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Proposal to NSF for An Investigation of Chloroplast DNA and its Replication, by Hanawalt, December 1962 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1963
  - Proposal to NASA for An Electron Paramagnetic Resonance Study of Unpaired Electrons in Photosynthetic Mutant and Wildtype Organisms, by Blois, January 1963. Also included is the Amendment of January, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Proposal to ONR for An Electron Paramagnetic Resonance Study of Unpaired Electrons in Photosynthetic Mutant and Wildtype Organisms, by Blois, January 1963 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Proposal to NASA for Plasma Physics and Related Topics of Astrophysics, by Sturrock, March 1963 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Proposal to ONR for Plasma Physics and Related Topics of Astrophysics, by Sturrock, March 1963 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Application to USPHS for Research Grant on Reducing Compounds in Serum in Renal Insufficiency, by Blois, June 1963 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Informal Proposal to Signal Corps for Studies of Transverse-Wave Interaction, by Chodorow, Wessel and Berg, August 1963 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Preliminary Proposal to ONR for Support of Research on Plasma Expanders, by Blois, August 1963 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Proposal to ONR for Molecular Physics and Photocatalysis with Coherent Light, by Schawlow, August 1963 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Proposal to the Advanced Research Projects Agency for Studies of Transverse-Wave Interaction, by Chodorow, Wessel and Berg, October 1963 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Application to Damon Runyon Memorial Fund for Cancer Research for The Incorporation of Melanin Precursors into Melanoma, by Blois, December 1963 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- PROPOSALS NOT ACTED UPON, 1964
  - Amendment to NASA Proposal SC 5642 dated January, 1963 for An Electron Paramagnetic Resonance Study of Unpaired Electrons in Photosynthetic Mutant and Wildtype Organisms, January 1964 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Proposal to NASA for Excited States in Biological Molecules, by Weissbluth, January 1964 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Proposal to AEC for Excited States in Biological Molecules, by Weissbluth, January 1964 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Application to USPHS for Excited States in Biological Molecules, by Weissbluth, January 1964 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Proposal to Wright-Patterson AFB for Magneto-Acoustic Resonance Phenomena for Device Applications, by Shaw, February 1964 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Proposal to NSF for A Research Project in Mechanism of Photosynthesis: Investigations Utilizing Electron Paramagnetic Resonance Spectroscopy, by Blois, April 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Proposal to NSF for Equipment Required for Execution of Investigations on the Mechanism of Photosynthesis, by Blois, April 1964 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Proposal to NASA for A Program in Computer Solutions of Vlasov Equations, by Kino, May 1964 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Proposal to ONR for The Mechanism of Photosynthesis: Investigations Utilizing Electron Paramagnetic Resonance Spectroscopy, by Weaver, May 1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Proposal to ONR for Equipment Required for Execution of Investigations on the Mechanism of Photosynthesis, by Weaver, May 1964 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Proposal to NASA for The Interaction of Electromagnetic Waves and Hypersonic Waves in Solids, by Chodorow, June 1964 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Proposal to NIH for Photosynthesis Mechanism: Research Using EPR Spectroscopy, by Weaver, June 1964 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Proposal to NSF for Studies of Tacticity and Morphology of Abiogenic Polypeptides, by Pattee, August 1964 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Proposal to NASA for Studies of Tacticity and Morphology of Abiogenic Polypeptides, by Pattee, August 1964 (Box 33, Folder 9)